http://www.amanapublications.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
POLICIES
GENERAL TERMS & CONDITIONSMETHODS OF ORDERINGPRIVACY POLICYRETURN & REFUND
PRIVACY POLICY
• We are committed to protecting our customer’s privacy and the information collected about our customers is strictly used for purposes of processing orders, and for notifying customers about the status of their order.
• The information we collect when orders are placed are Customer name, mailing address, credit card number and its expiration date.
• When orders are placed, amana publications uses a secure server.
• The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information that is fed into it before directing it to amana publications thereby ensuring secure privacy of customer data.
• Whenever we change our privacy policy, customers will be notified through our web page so that they are kept abreast of the changes effected. This way customers will be kept aware of the information we collect about them, how we use it, and under what situations and circumstances we disclose it.
• Amana publications does not sell nor provide its customer database, mailing list or email proprietary information to any outside organization.
• We are open to suggestions you may like to share with us concerning the Privacy Policy we have formulated. Your feedback can be sent to us at amana@amana-corp.com
Categories
About us
Catalogue
The Qur'an
Prophets
Classical Text and Jurisprudence
Culture and Civilization
Interfaith
GENERAL TERMS & CONDITIONSMETHODS OF ORDERINGPRIVACY POLICYRETURN & REFUND
POLICYSHIPPING POLICY
Contact us
Copyright 2020 Amana Publications : Sitemap
: Ecommerce Solution by BigCommerce
All prices are in USD.
